{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Closet Companies","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/2102382/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":2102382,"taskName":"Closet - Build","taskDescription":"Build a New Closet","xmTaskDescriptor":"Closet Companies","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":44,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Carpenter custom carpentry organizer walk-in","textMessagingName":"Build Closet","rolloverLongDesc":"Build a new closet in your home where one did not exist","rolloverShortDesc":"Build a new closet where one did not exist","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Build a New Closet.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Build a Closet \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Closet Companies","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":9,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Build Closet","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Closet - Build","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Custom Closet Builder Need","urlName":"Closet-Build","taskConsiderationId":3,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Closet Building Companies - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Carpenter,custom,carpentry,organizer,walk-in,oversized,closet,storage, walk, in","emcCategoryOid":-12010,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":801,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/2102382/":{"taskOID":2102382,"originalTaskOID":2102382,"setID":801,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":5803,"questionDisplayText":"Location of Closet","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where will the closet be located?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3770,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Master Bedroom","answerDisplayText":"Master Bedroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1003,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Bedroom","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2909,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Hallway","answerDisplayText":"Hallway","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":983,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Bathroom","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2716,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Garage","answerDisplayText":"Garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2248,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Entryway / foyer","answerDisplayText":"Entryway / foyer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3476,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Laundry / utility room","answerDisplayText":"Laundry / utility room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":958,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Basement","answerDisplayText":"Basement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5802,"questionDisplayText":"Closet Features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What features would you like to be included in the new closet? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1181,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Built-in shelves","answerDisplayText":"Built-in shelves","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1456,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Closet rod for hanging clothes","answerDisplayText":"Closet rod for hanging clothes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3594,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Lighting","answerDisplayText":"Lighting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3859,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Mirror","answerDisplayText":"Mirror","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6764,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Wall texture","answerDisplayText":"Wall texture","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500804,"questionDisplayText":"Part of a larger home remodel?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this part of a larger home remodel?","shortQuestionText":"Is this part of a larger home remodel?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":5803,"questionDisplayText":"Location of Closet","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where will the closet be located?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3770,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Master Bedroom","answerDisplayText":"Master Bedroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1003,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Bedroom","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2909,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Hallway","answerDisplayText":"Hallway","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":983,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Bathroom","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2716,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Garage","answerDisplayText":"Garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2248,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Entryway / foyer","answerDisplayText":"Entryway / foyer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3476,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Laundry / utility room","answerDisplayText":"Laundry / utility room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":958,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Basement","answerDisplayText":"Basement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3770,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Master Bedroom","answerDisplayText":"Master Bedroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1003,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Bedroom","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2909,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Hallway","answerDisplayText":"Hallway","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":983,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Bathroom","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2716,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Garage","answerDisplayText":"Garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2248,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Entryway / foyer","answerDisplayText":"Entryway / foyer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3476,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Laundry / utility room","answerDisplayText":"Laundry / utility room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":958,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Basement","answerDisplayText":"Basement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5802,"questionDisplayText":"Closet Features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What features would you like to be included in the new closet? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1181,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Built-in shelves","answerDisplayText":"Built-in shelves","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1456,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Closet rod for hanging clothes","answerDisplayText":"Closet rod for hanging clothes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3594,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Lighting","answerDisplayText":"Lighting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3859,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Mirror","answerDisplayText":"Mirror","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6764,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Wall texture","answerDisplayText":"Wall texture","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1181,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Built-in shelves","answerDisplayText":"Built-in shelves","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1456,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Closet rod for hanging clothes","answerDisplayText":"Closet rod for hanging clothes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3594,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Lighting","answerDisplayText":"Lighting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3859,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Mirror","answerDisplayText":"Mirror","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6764,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Wall texture","answerDisplayText":"Wall texture","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500804,"questionDisplayText":"Part of a larger home remodel?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this part of a larger home remodel?","shortQuestionText":"Is this part of a larger home remodel?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}